(Leonard:)You'll never guess
what just happened.
(Sheldon:)You went out in the hallway,
(Sheldon:)stumbled into
an interdimensional portal
(Sheldon:)which brought you 5,000 years
into the future,
(Sheldon:)where you took advantage
of the advanced technology
(Sheldon:)to build a time machine,
and now you're back
(Sheldon:)to bring us all with you
to the year 7010
(Sheldon:)where we are transported
to work at the Thinkatorium
(Sheldon:)by telepathically controlled
flying dolphins?
(Raj:)No.
(Sheldon:)Aw.
(Leonard:)Penny kissed me.
(Sheldon:)Well, who would ever guess that?
What-what kind of a kiss?
(Leonard:)A big kiss. On the mouth.
(Howard:)Is it possible that she was
going for your cheek
(Howard:)and you moved
and she accidentally got lip?
(Howard:)That happens with me and my mom
all the time.
(Leonard:)She introduced me to her father,
(Leonard:)kissed me and then
shut the door in my face.
(Howard:)Maybe she was trying
to send you a message.
(Leonard:)You think?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
"This man is not my father.
"I'm being held hostage.
"So I'm going to do
"something insane in the hopes
that you'll call 911."